=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 14=
= الحلقة 14 =
Watch out.
احذر.
Where's my handbag?
أين حقيبتي؟
Give it back.
أرجعها.
Isn't it hanging on your shoulder?
أليست معلقة على كتفك؟
Hurry and give it back.
اسرع واعيدها
Listen up.
اسمع.
There are many treasures in my handbag.
هناك العديد من الكنوز في حقيبتي.
Let me show you.
دعني اريك.
I'm going to make a fortune!
سأجني ثروة!
Listen.
استمع.
As long as it sells like hotcakes...
طالما أنها تبيع مثل الكعك الساخن ...
No,
رقم،
it'll definitely sell like hotcakes.
سوف تبيع بالتأكيد مثل الكعك الساخن.
All right.
حسنا.
Sit properly.
الجلوس بشكل صحيح.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Let me restore your primal eyebrows.
دعني أستعيد حاجبيك البدائيين.
You look adorable
تبدو رائعا
with your bushy eyebrows.
بحاجبيك كثيفين.
Why are you laughing like that?
لماذا تضحك هكذا؟
Enough.
كافية.
Sit properly.
الجلوس بشكل صحيح.
I'll get some hangover medicine for you.
سأحضر لك بعض الأدوية المخمرة.
Swimming in the vast sea!
السباحة في البحر الشاسع!
Full of water. A toad...
مليئة بالماء.  الضفدع...
A toad has four legs!
الضفدع لديه أربع أرجل!
-When you walk too often in the dark, -What are you doing?
- عندما تمشي كثيرًا في الظلام - ماذا تفعل؟
you'll encounter ghosts!
ستواجه أشباح!
Pass them to me.
مررها لي.
Come on.
هيا.
My dear lady,
يا عزيزي سيدة،
stop swimming.
توقف عن السباحة.
No.
رقم.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
I'll keep swimming.
سأستمر في السباحة.
I'll bring you to a larger pool later.
سوف آخذك إلى حمام سباحة أكبر لاحقًا.
Take your medicine first.
خذ دوائك أولاً.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Take your medicine first.
خذ دوائك أولاً.
If so, I want you to feed me.
إذا كان الأمر كذلك ، فأنا أريدك أن تطعمني.
Here.
هنا.
Are you awake?
هل انت مستيقظ؟
What time is it?
أي ساعة؟
Do you know
هل تعرف
that the cake you ate last night
أن الكعكة التي أكلتها الليلة الماضية
contained peach powder?
يحتوي على مسحوق الخوخ؟
I didn't know.
لم أكن أعرف.
Liu Yinshu was the one who ordered the cake.
كان Liu Yinshu هو الشخص الذي طلب الكعكة.
I know that.
وأنا أعلم ذلك.
If so, did you know she tried to set you up?
إذا كان الأمر كذلك ، فهل تعلم أنها حاولت إعدادك؟
What are you guys doing here?
ماذا تفعلون هنا يا رفاق؟
You took the words right out of our mouths.
لقد أخرجت الكلمات مباشرة من أفواهنا.
Ms. Liu,
آنسة.  ليو ،
what are you doing in Mina's warehouse
ماذا تفعل في مستودع منى
instead of sleeping at this hour?
بدلا من النوم في هذه الساعة؟
Did you guys tail me?
هل ذيلتموني يا رفاق؟
We were suspicious of you
كنا نشك فيك
ever since you tried to harm Weiyi
منذ أن حاولت إيذاء ويي
with the peach cake.
مع كعكة الخوخ.
We knew you had conspired with our rival company in secret.
كنا نعلم أنك قد تآمرت مع الشركة المنافسة لنا في الخفاء.
You hid a needle inside a lipstick.
لقد أخفيت إبرة داخل أحمر الشفاه.
You've committed the crime of producing and selling
لقد ارتكبت جريمة الإنتاج والبيع
counterfeit goods.
السلع المقلدة.
This can even be considered malicious assault.
يمكن اعتبار هذا حتى اعتداء ضار.
You can be sentenced to jail for this.
يمكن أن يحكم عليك بالسجن لهذا الغرض.
You're so vicious.
أنت شرير جدا.
It's all because of you!
كله بسببك!
I had been working in this position tirelessly
كنت أعمل في هذا المنصب بلا كلل
for many years!
لعدة سنوات!
Now you become my superior
الآن أصبحت رئيستي
just because you clinched a deal with HB!
فقط لأنك أبرمت صفقة مع HB!
That's so unfair!
هذا غير عادل!
If you feel wronged, we can have a fair competition.
إذا شعرت بالظلم ، فيمكن أن تكون لدينا منافسة عادلة.
However, you infringed
ومع ذلك ، أنت انتهكت
the rights of the consumers just so you could harm me.
حقوق المستهلكين فقط حتى يمكن أن تؤذيني.
You're so heinous.
أنت شنيع جدا.
(Warehouse)
(مستودع)
Thank you for saving me from the embarrassment that day,
شكرا لإنقاذي من الإحراج في ذلك اليوم ،
which also helped me discover Liu Yinshu's plot.
مما ساعدني أيضًا في اكتشاف مؤامرة Liu Yinshu.
If so,
لو ذلك،
Weiyi, can you thank me with some practical actions?
وييي ، هل يمكنك أن تشكرني ببعض الإجراءات العملية؟
Yes, as long as it's within
نعم ، طالما أنها في الداخل
my abilities.
قدراتي.
If so,
لو ذلك،
Weiyi, can you keep me company at my home for a while?
وييي ، هل يمكنك أن ترافقني في منزلي لبعض الوقت؟
Do you still remember this?
هل مازلت تتذكر هذا؟
I gave it to you
أنا أعطيتها لك
when we first dated each other, didn't I?
عندما واعدنا بعضنا البعض لأول مرة ، أليس كذلك؟
It's been so many years since then.
لقد مرت سنوات عديدة منذ ذلك الحين.
You still keep it with you?
هل مازلت تحتفظ به معك؟
You can buy anything you want right now.
يمكنك شراء أي شيء تريده الآن.
This is different.
هذا مختلف.
You said I was talented at fixing things
قلت إنني موهوب في إصلاح الأشياء
when you gave this to me.
عندما أعطيتني هذا.
You told me to study hard.
قلت لي أن أدرس بجد.
After that, I did study hard
بعد ذلك ، درست بجد
and became
و اصبح
a top mechanic in America.
ميكانيكي كبير في أمريكا.
After that,
بعد ذلك،
I spent the money I earned
لقد أنفقت المال الذي كسبته
to learn new things about the Internet.
لتعلم أشياء جديدة عن الإنترنت.
That's how I became who I am.
هكذا أصبحت من أنا.
Yeah.
نعم.
I knew you were something special.
كنت أعلم أنك كنت شيئًا مميزًا.
You will definitely succeed
سوف تنجح بالتأكيد
as long as you're willing to work hard.
طالما أنك على استعداد للعمل الجاد.
So, Weiyi,
لذا ، وييي ،
you're my benefactor.
أنت فاعل خير.
How could I bear to throw away
كيف يمكنني أن أتحمل أن أتخلص منه
the things you had given me?
الأشياء التي أعطيتني إياها؟
♪I'm loving you♪
♪ أنا أحبك
Since when have you been involved with art?
منذ متى وأنت متورط في الفن؟
You have good taste.
لديك ذوق جيد.
I drew it on a whim
رسمتها لمجرد نزوة
just to kill time.
فقط لقتل الوقت.
It looks pretty good.
تبدو جيدة.
♪Love should be taken care of♪
الحب يجب أن يعتني ♪
I need to get this.
أنا بحاجة للحصول على هذا.
All right.
حسنا.
♪I'm loving you♪
♪ أنا أحبك
♪If you love me too♪
♪ إذا كنت تحبني أيضًا ♪
♪Don't stand aside and keep quiet♪
♪ لا تقف جانبًا وتلتزم الصمت ♪
Bai Zeliu!
باي زيليو!
What is this?
ما هذا؟